Switchmen's Union of North America Records 5034
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Individual Carrier Agreement and Strike Files (Rocky Mountain-Southern Pacific) (Box 43)
  - Agreement and strike File: Sanderson and Porter Construction Company - Agreement, correspondence, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Santa Fe - Form agreement, 1901 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Santa Fe - Correspondence, representation, 1946-1952 (Box 43, Folder 29)
    Correspondence. 1946, 1951-1952
  - Agreement and Strike File: South Buffalo, 1919-1952 (Box 43, Folder 30)
    Correspondence. 1919, 1920, 1931-1934, 1937-1939, 1950-1952
  - Agreement and Strike File: Southern Pacific - Correspondence, 1901 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Southern Pacific Railway - Correspondence, 1921-1937 (Box 43, Folder 32)
    Correspondence. 1921, 1923, 1935- 1937.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Southern Pacific - Miscellaneous, 1943-1947 (Box 43, Folder 33)
    Correspondence. 1943, 1947
  - Agreement and Strike File: Southern Pacific - Organizing material, 1950 (Box 43, Folder 34)
- Individual Carrier Agreement and Strike Files (Southern Pacific-Terminal Railroad Company Texas) (Box 44)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Southern Pacific - Overtime case to disputes board, 1952-1953 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Southern Pacific - Agreements, correspondence, 1952-1955 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    Correspondence. 1952, 1953, 1955.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Southern Pacific - Strike, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Southern Pacific - Agreement, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, bound volume.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Southern Pacific - Agreement claim, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Southern Pacific - Objection to Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen affiliation with AFL-CIO, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    AFL-CIO: American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations. Correspondence.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Southern Pacific - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen/Switchmen's Union of North America propaganda, 1958 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Southern Pacific - Agreements, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Southern Pacific - Minutes of General Adjustment Commission, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Southern Pacific - Special Board of Adjustment, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Southern Pacific - Agreement Committee, decisions Switchmen's Union of North America versus Southern Pacific, 1960- 1963 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Southern Pacific - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen election propaganda, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Southern Pacific - Organizing, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Southern Pacific - Organizing material, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Southern Pacific - Vacation agreement claims, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Southern Pacific - Claims, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Southern Pacific - Wage Section 6 notice, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Agreement and strike File: Southern Pacific - Correspondence regarding election, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Spokane International - Correspondence, wage notice, agreement rates, rules and regulations, 1943-1966 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    Correspondence. 1943, 1945, 1957, 1963, 1966.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Spokane, Portland, Seattle - Miscellaneous, 1951-1954 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Southern Railroad - Railway Labor Executives Association subsidiary properties, correspondence, 1951-1966 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    Correspondence. 1951, 1966
  - Agreement and Strike File: Standard Oil Company - Concessions to Switchmen's Union of North America by Standard, 1916 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Stockton Terminal and Eastern - Schedule of pay and regulations, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Stockton Terminal and Eastern - Agreement, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Tennessee Coal and Iron - Miscellaneous, 1938-1939 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Tennessee Coal and Iron Railway, 1939 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Tennessee Coal and Iron - Miscellaneous, 1940-1941 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Tennessee Coal and Iron - Miscellaneous correspondence, National Labor Relations Board number 4740, 1942-1944 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Tennessee Coal and Iron - National Labor Relations Board certification of representation, 1943 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Tennessee Coal and Iron - Miscellaneous, agreement, 1943-1944 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Tennessee Coal and Iron - Correspondence on various cases, 1945 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Terminal Railroad Association of Saint Louis - Miscellaneous, 1922-1926 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Terminal Railroad Association of Saint Louis - Miscellaneous, rules and regulations, 1930-1934 (Box 44, Folder 33)
    Correspondence. 1930, 1934.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Terminal Railroad Association of Saint Louis - Miscellaneous, 1942-1949 (Box 44, Folder 34)
    Correspondence. 1942, 1948-1949
  - Agreement and Strike File: Terminal Railroad Company Texas - Miscellaneous, 1937 (Box 44, Folder 35)
- Individual Carrier Agreement and Strike Files (Texas City Terminal-Union Railway Company) (Box 45)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Texas City Terminal - Schedule of wages and working conditions, 1919 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Texas Electric - Miscellaneous, 1939-1940 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Texas and New Orleans Railway - Schedule of pay, agreement, 1901-1920 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    Correspondence. 1901-1902, 1910, 1920.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Texas and New Orleans - Miscellaneous, 1936-1958 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    Correspondence. 1936, 1944, 1958
  - Agreement and Strike File: Texas and New Orleans - Organizing material, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Texas and New Orleans - Organizing for election, 1964 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Texas and New Orleans - Wage notice, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Texas and Pacific Railway Company - National Railroad Adjustment Board and related correspondence, 1935-1940 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Texas and Pacific Railway Company - Correspondence regarding hospitalization, 1957 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Texas and Pacific Railway - Union shop hearing, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Texas and Pacific Railway Company - Claims, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Agreement and Strike file: Texas Pacific and Missouri, Pacific Terminal of New Orleans, 1957-1965 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    Correspondence. 1957, 1965
  - Agreement and Strike File: Toledo and Ohio Central - Limitation agreement, 1934-1935 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Toledo and Ohio Central - Miscellaneous, 1947 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Toledo and Peoria, Western - Miscellaneous, 1941-1942 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Toledo and Peoria, Western - Strike File, 1944-1947 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Trumbull Steel Company - Rules and regulations (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Union Depot Company - Agreements, Correspondence, 1954-1964 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    Correspondence. 1954, 1957, 1964.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Union Depot - Wage notice, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Union Pacific Railway - Miscellaneous, 1921-1945 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Union Pacific - Sutton versus Nichols dispute, 1923 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Union Pacific - Correspondence honoring Mr. Jeffer's promotion to President of Union Pacific, 1937-1940 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Union Pacific - Organizing in Denver, 1942-1943 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Union Pacific - Organizing, 1943-1951 (Box 45, Folder 24)
    A-1 - C-1. Correspondence. 1943, 1951.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Union Pacific - National Railroad Adjustment Board case, 1943 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen versus Union Pacific concerning a Switchmen's Union of North America employee. Correspondence.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Union Pacific - Organizing, 1952 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Union Pacific - Organizing, 1953 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Union Pacific - Grievance Claim, 1953 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Union Railway Company - Correspondence regarding the Charles Garner Case, 1940 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Union Railway Company - Union Railway Company versus National Railroad Adjustment Board, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 30)
- Individual Carrier Agreement and Strike Files (Union Terminal and Saint Joseph-Youngstown and Northern Railway) and Arbitration Cases (NRAB 4-504 - NRAB 1-12096) (Box 46)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Union Terminal and Saint Joseph - Agreement, 1924-1954 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Correspondence. 1924, 1935, 1953- 1954
  - Agreement and Strike File: Vicksburg, Shreveport and Pacific - Rules and regulations, 1925 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Wabash Railway - Miscellaneous including pay rates, 1915-1964 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Correspondence. 1915, 1935, 1950, 1964
  - Agreement and Strike File: Western Cable Railway Company of Saint Louis - Schedule of pay and agreement, 1914 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Western Pacific Railway Company - Agreements, 1938-1947 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    Correspondence. 1938-1940, 1944, 1947
  - Agreement and Strike File: Western Pacific - Strike at Montgomery Ward, miscellaneous, 1940-1943 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    Correspondence.1940- 1941, 1943
  - Agreement and Strike File: Western Pacific - Various claims, 1945-1947 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Western Pacific - General Correspondence, 1948-1953 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Western Pacific - Disputes on national rules, agreement, 1948-1957 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Western Pacific - schedule of pay and regulations, 1950 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Western Pacific - Case of a. Tunsem, 1953-1959 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Western Pacific - General Session, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Western Pacific - declined cases, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Western Pacific - Minutes and correspondence, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    2a. Correspondence.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Western Pacific - General Correspondence, 1956-1959 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Western Pacific - Organizing, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Western Pacific - Claims, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Western Pacific - Wage notice section 6, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Wheeling and Lake Erie - Switchmen's Union of North America organizing, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Youngstown and Northern Railway - Full crew law, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Arbitration cases: Texas and Pacific Railway - National Railroad Adjustment Board Division 4 Award 504, 1946 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Arbitration Cases: Great Northern Railway - NRAB 4-748, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Arbitration Cases: New York Central (lines west of Buffalo) - NRAB 1-1958, 1937 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Arbitration Cases: Texas and Pacific Railway - NRAB 1-2580, 1935 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Arbitration Cases: Saint Louis-San Francisco - NRAB 1-3889, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Arbitration Cases: Minneapolis, Saint Paul and Sault Sainte Marie - NRAB 1-5219, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Arbitration Cases: New York Central (lines west of Buffalo) - NRAB 1-5593, 1941 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Arbitration Cases: New York Central (lines west of Buffalo) - NRAB 1-5965, 1941 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Arbitration Cases: New York Central (lines west of Buffalo) - NRAB 1-5996, 1941 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Arbitration Cases: Michigan Central - NRAB 1-6685, 1942 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Arbitration Cases: Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Chicago, Rock Island and Gulf - NRAB 1-7493, 1942 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Arbitration Cases: Michigan Central - NRAB 1-7499, 1942 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Arbitration Cases: Denver-Rio Grande Western - NRAB 1-9257, 1944 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Arbitration Cases: Denver-Rio Grande Western - NRAB 1-9531, 1944 (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - Arbitration Cases: Denver-Rio Grande Western - NRAB 1-9532, 1943 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - Arbitration Cases: Denver-Rio Grande Western - NRAB 1-9795, 1944 (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - Arbitration Cases: Denver-Rio Grande Western - NRAB 1-9796, 1944 (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - Arbitration Cases: Denver-Rio Grande Western - NRAB 1-9798, 1944 (Box 46, Folder 38)
  - Arbitration Cases: Michigan Central Railway - NRAB 1 Docket 10387, 10388, 11638-11640 numbers withdrawn, 1943 (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - Arbitration Cases: New York Central (lines west) - NRAB 1-10690, 1945 (Box 46, Folder 40)
  - Arbitration Cases: Denver-Rio Grande Western - NRAB 1-11197, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 41)
  - Arbitration Cases: Denver-Rio Grande Western - NRAB 1-12095, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 42)
  - Arbitration Cases: Denver-Rio Grande Western - NRAB 1-12096, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 43)
- Arbitration Cases (NRAB 1-12110 - NRAB 1-2218, withdrawn) (Box 47)
  - Arbitration Cases: Detroit Terminal - NRAB 1-12110, 1948 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration Cases: Detroit Terminal - NRAB 1-12123, 1948 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Arbitration Cases: Michigan Central - 1-12294-12295, 1948 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Arbitration Cases: Michigan Central - NRAB 1-12296-12298, 1948 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration Cases: Michigan Central - NRAB 1-12299-12301, 1948 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Arbitration Cases: Michigan Central - 1-12322, 1948 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Arbitration Cases: Michigan Central - NRAB 1-12323, 1948 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Arbitration Cases: Michigan Central - NRAB 1-12325-12326, 1948 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Arbitration Cases: Michigan Central - NRAB 1-12335, 1948 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Arbitration Cases: Detroit and Toledo Shoreline - NRAB 1-12540, 1948 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Arbitration Cases: Denver and Rio Grande Western - NRAB 1-12810, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Arbitration Cases: Detroit and Toledo Shoreline - NRAB 1-13061, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Arbitration Cases: Kansas City Southern - NRAB 1-13062-13068, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Arbitration Cases: Kansas City Southern - NRAB 1-13069-13073, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Arbitration Cases: Pere Marquette Railway - NRAB 1-13082, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Arbitration Cases: Southern Pacific - NRAB 1-13203, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Arbitration Cases: Michigan Central - NRAB 1-13234, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Arbitration Cases: Denver and Rio Grande Western - NRAB 1-13274, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Arbitration Cases: Denver and Rio Grande Western - NRAB 1-13386, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Arbitration Cases: Denver and Rio Grande Western - NRAB 1-13387, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Arbitration Cases: Denver and Rio Grande Western - NRAB 1-13388, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Arbitration Cases: Denver and Rio Grande Western - NRAB 1-13389, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Arbitration Cases: Michigan Central - NRAB 1-13596, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Arbitration Cases: Denver and Rio Grande Western - NRAB 1-14235, 1951 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Arbitration Cases: Denver and Rio Grande Western - NRAB 1-14326, 1951 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Arbitration Cases: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - NRAB 1-15079, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Arbitration Cases: Kansas City Southern - NRAB 1-16394, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Arbitration Cases: Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe - NRAB 1-16929, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Arbitration Cases: Delaware, Lackawanna, Western - NRAB 1-17051, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Arbitration Cases: Illinois Central Railway - NRAB 1-17251, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Arbitration Cases: Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific - NRAB 1-17259, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Arbitration Cases: Buffalo Greek - NRAB 1-17261, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Arbitration Cases: Chicago Great Western - NRAB 1-17410, 17640-17642, 17645, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Arbitration Cases: Southern Pacific - NRAB 1-17683-17684, 1956-1957 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Arbitration Cases: Chicago Great Western - NRAB 1-17966-17968, 1957 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - Arbitration Cases: Nashville, Chattanooga and Saint Louis, 1957 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - Arbitration Cases: Southern Pacific - NRAB 1-18234-18237, 18257-18261, 18263, 18272, 18274, 18275, 1957 (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - Arbitration Cases: Southern Pacific - NRAB 1-18287-18290, 18312, 18316, 18328-18330, 18502-18507, 1957 (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - Arbitration Cases: Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and Saint Louis - NRAB 1-18313, 1957 (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - Arbitration Cases: Chicago Junction - NRAB 1-18327, 1957 (Box 47, Folder 40)
  - Arbitration Cases: Chicago, Rock Island, Pacific - NRAB 1-19222, 19361, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 41)
  - Arbitration Cases: Denver and Rio Grande Western: NRAB 1-19699, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 42)
  - Arbitration Cases: Southern Pacific - NRAB 1-20073, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 43)
  - Arbitration Cases: Saint Louis-San Francisco, 1862 (Box 47, Folder 44)
  - Arbitration Cases: Southern Pacific - NRAB 1-20216, 20478, 20479, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 45)
  - Arbitration Cases: Southern Pacific - NRAB 1-20499, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 46)
  - Arbitration Cases: New York, Chicago, Saint Louis - NRAB 1-20510, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 47)
  - Arbitration Cases: Southern Pacific - NRAB 1-20511, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 48)
  - Arbitration Cases: Southern Pacific - NRAB 1-20611, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 49)
  - Arbitration Cases: Southern Pacific - NRAB 1-20865, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 50)
  - Arbitration Cases: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - NRAB 1-20914, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 51)
  - Arbitration Cases: Indiana Harbor Belt Railway - NRAB 1-20916, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 52)
  - Arbitration Cases: Chicago Great Western - NRAB 1-20921, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 53)
  - Arbitration Cases: Los Angeles Junction - NRAB 1-20927-20928, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 54)
  - Arbitration Cases: Central of Georgia - NRAB 1-20929, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 55)
  - Arbitration Cases: Chicago Great Western - NRAB 1-20940, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 56)
  - Arbitration Cases: Chicago Great Western - NRAB 1-21027, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 57)
  - Arbitration Cases: New Orleans Terminal - NRAB 1-21040, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 58)
  - Arbitration Cases: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - NRAB 1-21181, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 59)
  - Arbitration Cases: Houston Belt and Terminal - NRAB 1-21224, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 60)
  - Arbitration Cases: Norfolk and Western - NRAB 1-21227, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 61)
  - Arbitration Cases: New York, New Haven, Hartford - NRAB 1-21241, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 62)
  - Arbitration Cases - Denver and Rio Grande Western - NRAB 1-21367-21369 (withdrawn), 1945 (Box 47, Folder 63)
  - Arbitration Cases: Western Pacific Railway Company - NRAB 1-22188 (withdrawn), 1947 (Box 47, Folder 64)
  - Arbitration Cases: Denver and Rio Grande Western - NRAB 1-24867 (withdrawn), 1948 (Box 47, Folder 65)
- Arbitration Cases (NMB R-24 - NMB R-199) (Box 48)
  - Arbitration Cases: South Buffalo Railway - NMB #-24, 1834-1936 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration Cases: Vicksburg, Shreveport, Pacific, Alabama and Vicksburg (Illinois Central) - NMB R-25, 1931-1935 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    A-1 - C- 1. Correspondence.
  - Arbitration Cases: Texas and Pacific Railway - NMB R-27, 1834-1936 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Arbitration Cases: Saint Paul Bridge and Terminal - NMB R-45, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration Cases: Peoria and Pekin Union - NMB R-48, 1934-1935 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    A-4 - E-4. Correspondence.
  - Arbitration Cases: Detroit and Toledo Shore Line - NMB #-67, 1934-1942 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    A-E. Correspondence. 1934-1936, 1942
  - Arbitration Cases: New York, Chicago and Saint Louis - NMB R-74, 1934-1935 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Arbitration Cases: Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and Saint Louis - NMB R-113, 1934-1950 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    Correspondence. 1934-1935, 1938, 1948, 1950
  - Arbitration Cases: New York, Chicago, Saint Louis - NMB R-135, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Arbitration Cases: Union Railway Company - NMB R-140, 1934-1935 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Arbitration Cases: Lehigh Valley - NMB R-155, 1934-1947 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    Correspondence. 1934-1935, 1947.
  - Arbitration Cases: Great Northern - NMB R-199, 1935-1936 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    A-2 - J-2. Correspondence.
- Arbitration Cases (NMB R-204 - NMB R-623) (Box 49)
  - Arbitration Cases: Chicago great Western - NMB R-204, 1935 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration Cases: Minneapolis, Saint Paul, and Sault Sainte Marie - NMB R-229, 1936 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Arbitration Cases: Chicago Great Western - NMB R-243, 1936 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Arbitration Cases: Detroit Terminal - NMB R-261, 1936 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration Cases: Oklahoma Railway Company - NMB R-276, 1937 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Arbitration Cases: National Railway Labor Conference and Eastern, Western, Southeastern Carriers Conference - NMB Number 282, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Arbitration Cases: Akron, Canton and Youngstown Railway - NMB R-287, 1938 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Arbitration Cases: Detroit and Toledo Shore Line - NMB A-289, 1936-1937 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Arbitration Cases: Delaware, Lackawanna, Western - NMB R-291, 1938 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Arbitration Cases: Pere Marquette Railway - NMB R-318, 1936-1937 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    A-3 - D-3. Correspondence.
  - Arbitration Cases: Fort Street Union Depot Company - NMB R-323, 1933-1948 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    Correspondence. 1933-1937, 1939, 1941, 1948
  - Arbitration Cases: Alton and Southern Railway - NMB R-341, 1937 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Arbitration Cases: Cincinnati Union Terminal - NMB R-371, 1938 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Arbitration Cases: Manufacturers Railway Company - NMB R-383, 1938 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Arbitration Cases: Chicago Great Western - NMB R-389, 1938 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Arbitration Cases: Peoria and Pekin Union Railway Company - NMB R-399, 1937 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Arbitration Cases: Pere Marquette - NMB R-437, 1937-1941 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    Correspondence. 1937-1939, 1941
  - Arbitration Cases: Chicago Great Western Railway - NMB R-448, 1938 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Arbitration Cases: Detroit Terminal - NMB R-488, 1938 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Arbitration Cases: Fort Worth Belt - NMB R-503, 1938-1939 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Arbitration Cases: Alton and Southern - NMB R-507, 1938 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Arbitration Cases: Detroit Terminal - NMB R-512, 1938-1939 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Arbitration Cases: Minnesota Transfer - NMB R-548, 1939-1944 (Box 49, Folder 23)
    Correspondence. 1939-1940, 1944
  - Arbitration Cases: Detroit and Toledo Shore Line - NMB R-560, 1939 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Arbitration Cases: Fort Street Union Depot Company - NMB R-568, 1939-1940 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Arbitration Cases: Detroit Terminal Railway - NMB R-598, 1940 (Box 49, Folder 26)